well you know it's really slow yeah
make sure to follow me on Instagram
right here have fourteen point four K
follower assess like dial alright
come into my channel drop frame zero the
camera lags I know the camera lags
there's nothing we can do about that
toddler is welcome hello
diamonds skin one hello let me see if I
can zoom in on this alright I'm so we're
gonna lay down a ground rule right now
and the ground rule is we only talked
about minecraft so if you're not here to
talk about Minecraft get the out of my
channel that's right
minecraft we're gonna play minecraft
make a server I don't know how to do
this no no we're not making a server
we're playing solo minecraft cuz some of
y'all might put some hate speech in the
server and we can't have any hate speech
because hate speech is not related to
Minecraft and we're only here to talk
about Minecraft so let's let's its
booting up here
mo Jiang here this game was made by a
bro named knotch
now let's create a new world and what
should we call our world twitchy's which
we call our twitchy's River world not
much I'm really not very good at this
game
twitch verse alright game mode Oh
survival that sounds
let's go
there's a good place for me
should make me bigger all right so I
don't really know how to play this game
so I'm going to need your help I'm going
around my other world looking for copper
for a while and then I found out that
there was no copper or maybe there is
and it was all very confusing
alright so welcome to twitch verse let's
play some minecraft where the seeds Oh
Sees oh sweet all right I think we have
to go chop down the Train
it's lagging
is it lagging no all right oh it's
lagging I forgot to fix the lag I don't
know why it's lagging we're not dropping
frames video capture device this is a
very high-resolution display you know
what let's just lower the resolution on
the display you can't even make it lower
than that no no no no no no no pervert
okay cool
so now we have less resolution now we
can make this big maybe this'll a gloss
yeah the game's not lagging for me it's
only lagging for you
is that bad well it's bad all right cool
let's make some planks no one no dating
in San Diego right go we got sticks but
no really what I want to make is a
crafting table all right where do I want
to live you know what let's go far away
let's just travel for a bit if we play a
nice song about traveling this area is a
little bit deforested if you know what
I'm saying I DeForest Sharpe whole pod
I'm really not very good in Minecraft
guys but we're going out of here because
I don't want to be here this place kind
of sucks
it's like a like jellyfish and stuff
let's go somewhere cool
[Music]
cows chickens
just in case I need whatever sheep have
[Music]
all right
this looks like a pretty nice place for
a home wouldn't you say what's this way
don't sleep in the nether I know about
that one you know Loki PewDiePie did a
lot recently for this game's popularity
[Laughter]
it's just the same world everywhere
Syria looks a little depressed where's
the sugar cane was that it over there oh
is that it over there all that looks
nice what is that anybody who talks
about anything is do I have any mods
here can we ban anybody who talks about
anything that isn't minecraft oh sweet I
got sugar this is a nice place
sorry peg I might need what you have I'm
not sure what you have but I might need
it
all right get some blue flowers nah but
for reals what are we doing thank you
for subscribing thank you accidentally
okay see this just become a mod oh this
looks like a nice place to build a house
wouldn't you all say haven't found any
mines gay thing we need mines in
Minecraft but this is idyllic you guys
this is an idyllic place to build a
house I think all right let's set up my
crafting table I'm gonna set it up right
up here against this wall here now what
can we make
let's make a pickaxe I'll look at these
beautiful flowers oh this is also so
beautiful you know all right where
should we put the mine maybe right here
what's in here oh this looks like a
great spot for a mine but I need coal
don't I is there any coal here this mine
kind of sucks guys
ah let's go back to our home I don't
know if that's gonna be our home able to
take our crafting table with us
this area is a little sparse and
resources I think oops no no that what I
make stolen pickaxe maybe only colistin
I call this time perfect what was that
noise oh the game audio is coming
through the speakers into my mic so is
this bad the hell is this thing
Hey Hey I'm gonna die this isn't funny
run run
right yeah this is terrible I'm losing
in Minecraft can these things jump I'm
afraid if I stop to eat they'll attack
me Oh phew we lost them while I was a
terrible place to make a house oh I can
sprint oh that's sick yo you bros are
the best control to sprint guy I like
you all right what is this mountain this
mountain looks pretty cool right I'm not
an idiot
alt f4 to sprint guy how come in
friendly mines mines mines guys now four
mines just we're looking for my fine
cave that's a good plan I like that plan
I took the crafting table all right I
got it and leave it to the wolves
yo those wolves was those wolves was
shed where are these caves
oh this looks like such an idea like
forest spot oh is it getting dark I
think it's getting dark
all right well camp here I didn't find a
mind
who lights my house we can mine a little
while we sleep it's gonna be dark and I
don't have any coal for torches
wall down my house should I built it out
of cobblestone oh no my house flooded oh
that was close bros oh that was close
alright we're good now so I've heard
from professionals that you should never
mind straight down cuz one time I did
this and I fell in lava and it was a
terrible time I can't see that please
call
well we're not up to redstone logic
gates guys but really just kind of
bootstrapping our way here this should
be a great house if it had some light
you know
let me make myself in the water I wish I
could see though Debbie you're gonna be
nice there even monsters on video
settings brightness 100 percent you know
what let me do that oh I still can't say
thank you see you better cool flames can
that make coal oh no my pickaxe broke
well that's a terrible time no it's nice
about shitty pickaxes though is you can
just make a new one that's really not
that big a deal
I'll give you diamond pickaxe breaks
that's a bad day we should eat
well no I just realized if we don't get
a bed soon we're gonna have to start
over
I don't need for a bed make a wallet
stop let's go kill some sheep tomorrow
Oh guys I feel cool your boy your boy
you know what they tell you about never
giving up and never surrendering that's
what I just did right there and now we
got torches that's right
normal people torches oh ho wow this is
beautiful this is a beautiful house guys
you know living underground actually
seems pretty sweet so how do I build a
door I build or old or oh I don't know
no I can just take this apart yeah I
don't know what I'm gonna do with three
doors but you know better safe than
sorry
oops I put in the wrong place
Oh terrible Oh is it light out no still
dark out but at least we can mine let's
eat some money let's eat some raw pork
chop
can I eat sugar how come I can't eat
this can I turn it into something paper
huh sugar that should be edible all
right come I can't eat it
make furnace how do I make furnace it's
not a cobblestone furnace okay
I have furnace what you do I have
furnace what dough can I cook my sugar
[Music]
can I cook my sugarcane okay so while I
make a furnace Oh iron Wow I have an
iron would I get that is there iron back
here - oh this is a sick as mine ever am
i right
iron and coal
[Music]
oh yeah we about to move up in the world
boys
okay what do with all our new found
treasure I'm not gonna put the box near
the furnace because it might catch fire
is there a fast way to do this I saw I
saw this something like fast way
shift-click oh yo that's so fast yo all
right good
why do you do that maybe
cobblestone can come with me so we can
build things hi that's good
oh yeah we got in goths oh we definitely
need some stick as well let me stick a
couple oh thanks you know stick yeah
throw down two sticks that I'm some iron
in got ya buddy all right cool
all right can we uh nope it's still dark
outside
that's insane that is just really insane
just make myself a stone sword require
too much resource
how am I going to do with my doors they
can definitely stay here what a ways to
call alright
put your food in furnace I tried that
all its sun's rising sweet all right
wait do I get out oh no oh no oh wow I
hope I got flood insurance no okay well
this is terrible this is this is really
does I don't like this let's go this way
there is no water this time sweet okay
what do it today guys what do today
let's build a big things where I
remember where my house is sometime I
lose my house and that's a bad day
okay let's jump in the water should be
okay perfect
your move s and I can put that back
there ah beautiful look at my house
should make some cobblestone steps for
my house
maybe we all right
so first things first let's go get some
food I have set up sets me that I can't
be a vegan in Minecraft but I'm not very
good at farming so let's go see what
food we can find hey remember when there
was food everywhere and we didn't kill
it
that was stupid I don't know why we
didn't do that mmm we're even are we I'm
gonna lose my house it's not a mine oh
that's nice it's right by the house all
right cool you can go back there later
let's just get the stuff we need for a
bed I'm gonna have to kill sheep though
this doesn't make me happy set a pig up
there oh you're dead pig yeah you can
fence them in and breed them for food I
don't know I'm not really good at that
we can try what's that they're just
another mine
it might be monsters in that mine
Oh sheep wait if I kill them do I have
to share them do I ever get wall wall
perfect
I need your food straight up okay
three white wall I think that's all I
need
pack your chicken you live okay I recall
correctly my house is right over there
but sometimes I get lost let's see
should we cook this stuff cook this food
can I make like a fire campfire make a
campfire oh it's a lot of wood was
smithing table watching what is
fletching
here so that'd be nice to have stop
killing all those sheep I cost me iron
wooden sword or I can make arrows I
heard I think a bed yes bed
perfect well we should make myself a
nice bedroom you know there's a
one-bedroom apartment make a flint and
steel what do I do with that
can I start fires are you trolling me
that's nice perfect okay let's make a
flint and steel
Oh let it go well I'll cost me an iron
that better have been worth it oh wait
uh should we have the fire room let's
make a fire room behind the bed okay now
can I cook my chicken what
q to drop and that'll cook my chicken
guys how do I know when they're done you
put it all right
no no no you know what
I'm I'm tempted to just turn the stream
off no that was what why do I have this
is it a weapon
exactly me any food guys okay I need an
axe I'm very upset
that was incredibly disheartening you
know what because of you guys more
minecraft animals have to die you're
terrible people and I'm just killer you
know you know what I'm just gonna burn
the whole place down
that's right sorry you get fire and you
get fired you get fired that's right
that's right I'm lighting the whole
place on fire
well my fire burned out
it's spreading can I use my shears once
I share a chicken can't your chicken I
can't shoot that thing either wait how
do I use I want to share you yes thank
you
is that a horse can I ride it that's
right
yeah I'll find more horses that one was
food why not kill all the sheep I just
should have sheared you come here sheep
I want to share you I already sheared
you no more wall oh we got to go home
it's getting dark we're not making on
autonomous anything you guys you've seen
how noob I am at this game I threw all
my food in the fire let's go let's go
let's go let's go oh yeah wait control I
can run see sometime you guys give me
good tip so I'm like flint and steel oh
we have to chop a tree down quick oh
please use my shears to do this I
shouldn't be doing that I guess my iron
pickaxe will do
[Music]
oh my hunger decreases faster oh that's
why it's so low foods hard to get ha
home sweet home
all right who's ready for bed the fire
room whew
Oh cook food first that would have been
a smart idea all right well let's make a
campfire because I know that's actually
how you cook food guys it's that to a
green bed that's cool
campfire
oh we have to make more sticks
well I suffer from carbon monoxide
poisoning if I put this in here maybe we
should build a chimney
oh yeah those are be steaks in no time
taste is somehow monsters up there don't
really know where monsters come from but
then I coded them up there all right
perfect
for leather as well I make something
cool out of leather
should I use the furnace alright help me
out guys what do I do now
Oh rose bush alright let's make a hoe or
an axe I'll be fine with that
alright let's go home a bit of I
can't believe I wasted an eye on flint
and steel and it's the most useless
thing and it just burns your food never
run out of wood again this looks like
some great land for farming right here
huh well let's turn into wheats oh you
need water nearby
oh okay never mind I was kidding about
the weed is that true is that one of my
things ever work that's why I can't farm
oh okay well it's good to know what my
house go I'm lost
well good thing I built that little
tower to tell me okay let's just go
through water my things grow here nice
like that for blocks on the water
all right cool I'm out dirt dirt dirt
you are an edge to block
perfect
all right by the entrance to my house so
those are gonna grow oh there's a
cooldown on hitting Wow okay what do I
do
I'm confused let's go to the mind now we
just go get my food first
mmm steak oh that was delicious you guys
oh there's the best steak I've had in a
while oh you know what we got to build
some cobblestone stairs
maybe this will lessen fury at you guys
hah who likes my staircase
do you like my staircase oh it's a
beautiful staircase I think oh okay this
is kind of annoying because now these
things are in my way let's build a
cobblestone ring around them I'm trying
to dam up this whole river it's gonna
work where does the water come from how
is this all right here just paving this
place you know pig
explore knocked my torches back I'm
putting a wall up here so nobody will
ever come to this stupid place again how
that's one of my torture suppose you
gotta go back for it I don't know maybe
this place is cool I take it back
this could be my second home just give
you my summer okay what was that mine
let's go to the mine alright and I
understand you guys are offended that my
my farm is not symmetric you can go make
my farm symmetric later is my mind so I
know that big mine I found the other day
where was it I'll make a shield oh that
might have been a smart idea
I found the mine flooded not so long
ha iron underneath it don't mind
straight down
[Music]
remember your home coordinates press f3
I'm not pressing any day
I don't trust you but if you all want to
tell me what to do um down because I
don't really know what to do anymore
like I knew what to do I knew I had to
get iron and like we can look around for
diamond but like oh they have nests a
long way down
[Music]
who are found iron on my staircase
for now
[Music]
it's a long way down
see I made it symmetric just for you
guys okay press f3 Wow
[Music]
pretty cool okay are we going to the
bottom of the mind I think we are
should we make a shield first should
make a little home in here let's make a
little home in here set some stuff up I
[Music]
wish real life was like this would be
cool and you could just have a little
home anywhere
[Music]
you could like build things like this at
a rock furnaces are cheap oh I didn't
bring many of my doors with me to make
another door that's offensive should
make three more doors now we can't do
that as too many doors
you know whatever I'm gonna second
furnace kind of furnaces a lot and I
need a shield shield shield shield
shield shield our shield iron ingot and
my shield head
iron pickaxe is running out - oh there's
a creeper that's what those things are
called free verse I'm scared of it going
back to my house my house go you'll
don't come near my house bro can I shoot
it
can the furnace really catch things on
fire next to it
you're Blackwall I'm gonna blackball to
make a bed some logs down here mistakes
with me dandelion seeds and flowers and
stuff could stay here i season come with
me when you're gonna okay so how do I
kill that guy I build a bridge oh no
another one Oh my stairs my beautiful
stairs okay should we get to oh wow it's
nighttime
oh we got to go good thing I have
weapons not come upon any sheep this
year I really like to share a couple
sheep
you see an Enderman
who's an Enderman do I have that they
don't explode if you're around a corner
they say right down
what is that noise is a monster by my
fire I was definitely the most remote
and fire anymore
no we need a new iron pickaxe now I'm
gonna make one in my mind
what what no Eve anyway
some good steaks I'm gonna lead them
away from my crap when will the battle
in the guys pull the battle and what
make a bow with sticks and string I say
when I could be as annoying as that guy
I don't have that many steaks Oh sheep
I'm gonna shear you pick a black bed can
i okay can't share the chicken
what my mind go pick some all birds out
of that sheep all right I don't know I'm
not sure what to do next in this game I
feel like I already won I made a bed
dozen I mean you win mine yeah
eggsy your coordinates and why is your
level I guess behind
that's a lot of iron in gun
shooting at me let's go make an iron
sword I have one steak left also a
little concerning
Oh build a secret staircase let's build
a secret staircase
I forgot my doors I want to bring them
down here
I built the secret staircase right into
my house all right well we have a lot of
oak planks we'll just make more doors
oh I feel so safe in here come on alarm
let's make some iron armor you'd be
indestructible
I lost all my iron
and out of food to which I don't like
tiny grass you cannot eat grass is that
dirt it's like the Red Rock
I thought this was gonna connect okay so
what's the game mechanic
I don't know wait till it recharges just
when I die
oh he's attacking bow and arrow guy
that's a good deal and now I'm out of
food there's creepers well this is
another bone arrow guy we gotta go we
gotta go get food all right let's build
a secret staircase out of here
Cali California welcome to the
subscribers we don't have a name for you
guys you're just like good twitchy is
that what most kind of Suggs band who
ever talked about anything that wasn't
minecraft let's we only talk about
minecraft this is a minecraft channel
guys I know I'm not very good but one
day I dream that I can be as good as
who's that famous guy you know the
famous guy knotch
he's famous now that's not what I was
thinking about I was thinking about the
other famous guy um which famous guy was
I thinking about the guy who just quit
twitch because twitch put porn on his
stream you know Jake Paul
they're monsters up here now this is
dirt oh we found me up it's nighttime
all right oh that's pretty cool where am
i where am i go Korea where am I
what is this how it's lava come here
monsters we're monsters come here come
to the lava
oh I'm gonna die where's my house I
never remember where my - oh no this
isn't how it ends guys this isn't how it
ends that's a shoe there guy I'm trying
to think where I went I felt like I went
underground and this was fine you know
what can I just get back to my mind
where's my mind okay well here's lava
land my mind was safe
my mind was safe where's my mind there's
lava land no that's not my mind I'm
gonna kill you chicken just my mind
No Oh creeper no no oh oh that was close
I could have all gone much worse where's
my house
oh no I was closed off no no no no no no
not today no great okay let's sleep
tomorrow we go find my stuff okay oh we
have some wooden pickaxe a little bit of
coal no wood no food all right cool
perfect okay harvest us no the other one
wasn't ready to harvest
I get cool all right so I have a
strategy guys we're gonna go find my
stuff we're gonna go back and know how
to get to the mine yeah I could do that
but that would be sensible
yeah I'm now remembering my numbers
that's cheating you guys both like I
cheated video games
it's cheating thank you following
Instagram let's try it at your charts I
know all I have now is a wooden pickaxe
but one day I'll have an iron pickaxe
when I go find my iron pickaxe that I
had not very long ago all right so my
first strategy is to get back to where
we were it was nighttime everything was
dark it was all confusing first we're
gonna get back to my secret exit from my
house you'll notice I have installed a
beautiful door how so no monsters can
get in so we know this place is safe for
monsters
alright we're good now I'm like oh yeah
let's just build a secret exit okay cool
here's my secret exit you have five
minutes before you stop vanishes as
that's true already slept okay so first
off where Wow okay I'm already lost how
do I come out here no no no that's lava
how did I how did I come out here oh
here it is
okay hey we hold boomer okay so
you're like ran around for a bit got
attacked by some guy it did my stuff
really disappear
this is five minutes real oh
there's the entrance to the mine okay
well at least we know where we are it is
possible I went down the other side of
the hill
it was on the river it is also possible
my stuff fell in the river that should
mostly be our tack you know the stuff
wasn't even that great anyway what great
stuff that I have you didn't have shears
okay I think maybe we just cut our
losses and say that stuff sucked anyway
which kind of did it's going to the
right it could be on the other side of
this hill I think goes a river there
what's this that's a nice mine
they're cute sauce
don't see my stuff anywhere I don't even
have good stuff to begin with you know
into one loop around here and I were
just gonna give up cuz this stuff sucks
anyway is there a river on the other
side of this well I'm not ignoring chat
what do you want all right who knows
where to go
did someone watch this stream and tell
me where my stuff is
I feel like I did that
if anybody talks about that isn't
minecraft you know you're all banned
follow the river wheat river okay you
know what we're gonna Google Wow okay
now my monitors don't really work
because I change the resolution why I
just so much for you bros does your
stuff disappear in Minecraft after you
die perfect if they're on the ground for
five minutes
oh well that stuff sucked anyway that's
what I think
now I'm lost oh you're back wanna go
home alright this is now a Minecraft
mission we are gonna try to make it to
the nether after he is cheating we're
gonna make it to the nether and then
we're gonna call declare ourselves
minecraft heroes so let's see if we can
do that because I've never actually made
to the nether before there you have to
like just dunk water on lava click this
link to make a farm I made a farm
you don't like my farm never wheat I
don't like to make bread but no but I
don't really know where oh well this
sucks this isn't where we want to be
alright I went on a wild goose chase
after my stop and now I'm lost I should
build a campfire by the entrance and
then I could have seen the smoke for
miles
died so you can respawn at home you know
what I almost like that plan I don't
really have that much good stuff with me
that might not be a bad plan we'll do
that if we don't find a better plan
I could wander around in these crevices
for hours never find a thing it all
looks so familiar but then it's all just
bricks go to the right over the warning
I think that's right no this is
different water you guys
[Music]
no no I've been here before on a wild
goose chase looking for my stuff and I
deeply regret it it was bad stuff anyway
now it's left alright I trust you
twitchy's for the most part except for
f3 you haven't led me wrong no stop it
with f3 f3 is cheating and the people
who use f3 alike the people who uses
gps's in their car
oh who chopped this tree down had to
have been me do you guys really just not
get lost in this game oh you guys will
cheat use f3 don't give me that all
looks the same I agree okay gathered
some nice flowers I'll bring them home
to my why oh that's right now they
belong oh yeah I think it's this I think
it's this I think I know where I'm going
prediction to be confirmed we're gonna
run into the mine soon oh you know I did
have though I built all that expensive
armor yeah here's my mind Thomas Lee
where's the chicken you're gonna make a
nice steak for tomorrow Hey Oh
[Music]
I've never been so excited to go home
before going home
Oh almost home guys we're almost home at
the end of a long day turning brightness
not stopping with you guys just wanna
cheat you know y'all cheating at
Minecraft can I harvest these yeah
harvest my harvest that one yeah harvest
I walked on the other ones it's all a
bad for him
five three weeks oh let's make bread
let's settle down for a nice loaf of
bread tonight yeah I throw my steaks on
the oh yeah after mine I'll tell my beef
on that oh that's gonna be sick yeah
just go over here just throw down three
wheats oh yes a nice loaf of bread
tomorrow we'll expand the garden you're
gonna be an indoor rosebush don't catch
fire what good thing I always keep some
spare dirt there oh I wish I had some
iron ingots or something but I don't I
don't
so you know we get you got a stone
Wow how the mighty have fallen
oh we used to be rich when we used to
have everything defend with one careless
death we lost it and now we have nothing
at least we will have my rose bush oh
that's a beautiful rose bush alright I
won't carry too much with me next
time thanks minecraft hindsight captain
who thought we were gonna die
nobody not me well I woke up scarily
close to that campfire I have my steak
look my mistake
give me a steak I we're good alright we
got steak we got bread let's go to my
other house they're monsters we need a
home
just plant more stuff yeah we should
plant our star alright you be sticks no
wait why don't you just go to this mine
this is a nice mine we forgot a nice
this mine boys you know we went to that
other mind thinking that we were gonna
find stuff we're gonna find I'm
your found but you know this is a
nice mind too and it does have any
monsters in it now it's not trees - Alex
I know I need more food where do I get
it where do I get food
Zef food oh it's gonna make a home I
need to make a hole for you kill a cat
make cow farm okay I like that plan
let's make a cow farm you're right
before we even travel to the nether we
need to how do I get the cow to come
over here or I guess I can make a cow
farm anywhere
well breeding animals takes forever I
need to feel I need to feed them
weed why don't I just eat bread if I'm
gonna feed them we know I like the
plants they pissed me off I wanted
something that pisses them off and for
me it's plants off this cold you know
coal might not be much to some people
but to me who lost all his stuff in a
terrible accident
coal is lot sorry torch
okay you know what I'm sick of not
having iron we have on our knees need to
go get it it's not in this mine right
here yeah plant that's right
what I don't even have it if I could
just bake bread why don't I just make
bread wheat
oh yeah home sweet home number two where
I have lots of iron I believe actually I
think I wasted all my iron making armor
which I then lost well we have three
yard sweet
I'll settle for a stone sword
bread and steaks with more tasks we cook
the rotten flesh okay
my name is shir want a mining coal I
don't need call I want to get on so I
can make a bucket so I can get walk
let's go kill this guy look his iron
over there just took a guy you can't
even hit me down there can you see old
praise me on my patience in that
encounter by the way notice how I didn't
just bum-rush him who I found la la la
we call I was anticlimactic if it be
something cool down here nothing too
cool alright how do we get to the nether
guys oh that could be bad is that good
monstrous yeah it just sucks wait I need
diamond to get to the nether oh I guess
I need a diamond pickaxe in order to
break the nether Rock well I have coal
and iron so if that's what I need that's
what I have things are stupid
okay let's go find some diamond if we
need diamond we need a diamond too or
can I say doing it with buckets is kind
of massive don't tell me to mind
straight down okay we'll make a diamond
pickaxe no he's protecting his baby
be my over the under a letter - is that
gold
what kind of do with gold
Oh
you got noise come from Hey iron is
everything fine diamond what's that
noise
all right let's go back to my house not
ambient sounds of uses monster it's not
immediate well they're doing a good job
I'm scared my crash is scary what was
that we're how'd I get down here is it
up how this monsters over there I think
I'm supposed to go I'm lost again just
didn't help that this thing doesn't
render no that was that stupid place I
cleared out from the wah-bah
nope nope nope nope nope that's right
can't with me in here broski that's
just tunnel op am i at low enough level
to find diamonds let's check every I'm
at negative 40 I'm at 47 is that good
is there diamond tier level 11 how do
you know I'm at 37 I mean it says 48
I'll go diamonds near the lava
the middle one is your level oh I'm at
39 diamonds are at 11 diamond is below
16 okay well let's first go home and
then we're gonna go you know what we're
just gonna dig really deep this is it
you know what I got a plan guys we use
an f3 we're only using it we're not
using it to find things but we are using
it to tell how deep we are that's right
that's the plan I figured it out all
myself
let's get out of this terrible mind what
what even was that did the torch burn me
is that possible just my house no
andesite what a material our dirt
now what's the circus why don't you go
with the surface okay here we are again
and it's nighttime last time we did this
terrible things happened this time will
we be smarter first we're gonna leave
some torches so we know how to get back
in I'm at a tortoise
no no no no this isn't happening again
oh no that's right all right guys we're
just gonna chill we're just gonna we're
just gonna chill um that guy's gonna die
in the morning anyway then he sucks
that's what I've heard
I don't have any wood so I can't make
myself a house down here we could just
casually mined this iron skeletons don't
die in the Sun you know what let's just
go out a different way is this minecraft
or is this minecraft you know I wish I
knew the X Y Z of my house so I could
just tunnel back there you don't I'm
saying we wouldn't even have to see the
skeletons we could just tunnel I mean I
know it's a long tunnel but like if el
chavo can do it I think we can do it too
I wish we had some sticks and some wood
okay let's go to the surface
let's get sticks and wood
creeper no cat every time we go to the
surface
bad things happen I'm out of food I'm
starving to death here in this mine like
the moves to remember the Chilean miners
it's like me it's pretty nice though
these torches you should keep the
monsters away where's my house
okay welcome to our new home
I'm not going outside cuz it's sketchy
out there there's monsters and but
this is our new home
nice crafting table in it it's amazing
how you can find everything you need
just underground to make like furnaces
and crap yeah buddy oh yeah then we dump
our iron in here make another one of
those furnaces are gold and that one
okay
to make a couple more torches what a
deal see where we can't make food or bed
but those things be different oh it's
daytime let's go home henceforth oh no
oh no oh no
okay well good thing I didn't have
anything good
now the only question is can we find
that place again let's go we got five
minutes a wheat cake who remembers where
that place was I think I was super close
yeah
it's not the skeleton that killed me my
stop ready yeah
it's gonna feel good to kill you man
that's right
okay so torch land is somewhere around
here to that islands Wow look how close
it is to my house oh this is the new
best entrance to the mine okay how's my
iron smelting going really well
as to be expected got myself a new iron
pickaxe beautiful okay and now we begin
the project
oh it's super close to our house this is
the most convenient armored shield
shovel that's no stop shooting me bro oh
it's so conveniently located by our
house okay guys ctrl + left click to get
things oh I see what you're saying
Oh wheat okay we're just gonna go for
diamonds what level do I have to go to
[Music]
welcome to the new step mine
nothing can kill us in the step mine we
have torches in the step mine anymore
what you'll have one in my box you know
what we gotta go whit hunting use the
sword
that's good what this is good
I need to plant more wheat but then I
have to make a hoe and I don't want to
do that I know ax gets wood faster yeah
type my home chords and chat guys know
we're at 58 and we're about to go down
this is for all the miners who said that
you have to explore to play Minecraft
we're gonna go down and we're gonna
strip mine till we get a diamond mine
because we are gamers and we have no
limits to what our patients can hold if
I can play old-school World of Warcraft
which I hear is really popular right now
and slay 15 dingbats and then go slay 50
Rumplestiltskin zand it's the same task
as the dingbats they've just called
something different because the creators
are lazy we can get to the end of the
earth in Minecraft where there is tons
and tons of diamonds is that what I'm
saying who believes in us 43 42 41 yeah
here we go what number do I have to be
at 4 diamonds
eleven let's go guys if I go to eleven
do I die is it all lava you guys
with me why you even found iron boots in
my stairs so we can mark I feel like I'm
building a Soviet missile shelter you
know you just dig down and build a big
room at the bottom bought some wood with
us everyone will feel at home I mind
straight down that was horrifying
right here 14 13 what's it zero 12 11
welcome to 11 now we're gonna find
diamond no diamond that way
we're not hacking the game guys we're
here to play Minecraft you're not here
to hack minecraft we're here to play
minecraft
anyone can hack minecraft but does
everybody have the patience to dig all
the way down to level 11 to grind
endlessly through these mines until we
find diamonds is there a more efficient
way to do this desert f3 but tells you
what a diamond is I don't want to talk
about food I don't know how to get it
don't worry I have enough wood for a
crafting table
oh well good I'm gonna need that soon
okay well this sucks that whole card are
contained zero diamond where the
staircase go over here
is there really Dimond at 11 I don't see
it I didn't see any redstone ore lapiz
lazuli Oh red stop
know what to do with it all so much
redstone only that was all diamond
automatic miner
I'm just digging tunnels is more
efficient or cut tunnels it is mine long
straight holes all right I'm on where's
the diamond they're making another
pickaxe this is a waste of mine
so that was that the auto diamond
locator do you see anything I'm looking
torches so
oh man this is brutal
I remember just stumbling upon Dimond
once that was a good day that's good to
hear right now stick with one tunnel
[Music]
if all this redstone was diamond we'd be
rich
I mean do it all those rock this is
terrible
slowly subject our children to this is
like work simulating what a minute
diamond in there oh what's that
lapiz lazuli
oh man don't
oh what's that
coal's did I forget to enable diamonds
and now we're out of pickaxe
where are my diamonds look at the size
of his mind oh man I've whatever when I
thought the digging was gonna be the
hard part
yeah I know about running but it cost me
food Oh
can I open this server to you guys come
help me mine diamonds wow that was a
long walk okay
can I sleep now a break from our
regularly scheduled programming of
diamond mining where we're gonna build
something large out of all our
cobblestone
[Music]
and want to put that one there
Wow that takes a really long time okay
that was terrible so the wheat bro we
gotta go put
this is our big stone thing do you like
it do you like how symmetrical it is
good I worked hard on what I will this
stone can I do with it I'm gonna iron
got a have on let's make a pickaxe first
need to make stick okay we're going to
look for diamond guys wish us luck if we
don't get diamond then we're gonna be
devastated
ah yeah next time if we do another
minecraft stream next time I don't need
food if we do another minecraft stream
we'll do multiplayer next time but I'm
never playing this game again because
it's terrible and I don't know how we
subject our children to this no it's not
really terrible I'm just bad at it I've
been looking for diving for a long time
and I haven't found it it's kind of
sucked and it's kind of its kind of a
disheartening because I've dug so far
and still no diamond I don't know if you
guys are trolling me about 11 you know
what we're gonna check we're gonna check
or am I being trolled minecraft what
level is diamond perfect most common in
layers 5 through 12
oh we could go deeper we need to go
deeper
let's try digging a little deeper maybe
we are in a deep server
is that the diamond noise I bet if I had
a diamond miner I could get through the
bedrock house they're still cold I
killed all the coal ate that's a good
place to find damage
oh that's a good point maybe I should
look by the call
maybe it's by the cult it sounds like a
good idea just follow where diamonds
come from this is brutal
oh okay where's that cold they're
diamonds by that right here
[Music]
it's the big cold opossum there's got to
be some diamond around here
iron they've got everything here
[Music]
dirt
as the diamond where's the diamond
[Music]
more redstone no I'm gonna have to make
another pickaxe in a minute
[Music]
we're running low on stick
it can't be monsters down here can now I
built this mine with my own hands
[Music]
well it doesn't make sense you came near
BA it's a diamond dinner huh monsters
get into the go
wait is that diamonds it's coal take it
it's almost diamonds why should I sit -
one time can someone give me actual
logic why I should stick to one tone oh
mind everything here damn in a spare
I think we might be out of sticks
therefore we're out of torches and
therefore we can't see and therefore
there's no guy
I don't even remember how to get out of
here no dime in there there diamond tier
no diamond here right : so we have to go
back to the surface and get more
[Music]
come on diamond well there's coal with
his coal there's diamonds found another
coal land and now we don't have any more
pickaxes use the AG this is terrible
this games
terrible I don't know anybody who played
who plays this game I've been digging
for diamond for so long you guys aren't
even trawling i Gogol dance
all right we need an axe somebody stick
that sucks
I don't even know what the Enderdragon
is I'm going to the nether and we're
gonna go hang out there no and then
we're ending this thing because if we
make it to the nether we did everything
we meant to do all right who wants to do
some outdoor crafts let's do some
outdoor crafts first things first I'm
gonna make an axe no longer and I make
an axe I need to make stick first no
longer are we going to chop trees with
an inferior non house and all these
trees are gonna die for my lack of
d'arnot
then it's not what I want to a dirt
Louie's didn't wants to eat and even
want most of that stuff factor oh wow
this is a nice farm actually thanks
creeper did he blow up my crafting table
you did I was just doing some outdoor
crafts you know what I won't make anyone
we've an axe we have a sword give a
shovel
sorry it's stone I'm gonna make a hoe
I'm gonna plant our wheat seeds not a
stick
no I didn't want an axe no put it back
one of the ho that's what I wanted there
we go
does that work
[Music]
all right throw it you know what if it
worked for drama
we'll build a wall
now no creepers can come with me so
many of these things Oh
music what is this turbo build mode I
thought that will have to be removed
from for a night because it was too good
control Q throw everything through
wonder
[Music]
White's my farm okay back to the diamond
mine
Oh diamonds by branch mining oh okay
good I like learning let's learn branch
mining is safer than more reliable than
caving
whoa I don't even know how that makes
sense okay I'm done I don't even know
guys we're gonna do it we're gonna find
Dimond we're gonna go to the nether and
we're gonna we're gonna hit that's it
that's it for the minecraft stream the
sir he went on way too damn long this
was supposed to be over quickly but it's
not because everything in Minecraft
takes forever all right so first off
there's a car door somewhere without
torches let's find it
forget it branch mining because like
this a different branch like a branch of
our division my name's to all cheats
that tell me where the diamond is
look at the memory how rare is this
go back up to 11 I heard it's the
optimal lair for diners those lots of
good here got gold again iron got
coal up this has gotta be off ways of
diamonds oh yeah it's no way cuz
diamonds just not real
lapiz lazuli
I got doomed I thought it was dying
[Laughter]
these diamonds I'll be nice about a
shovel you can make one
oh don't think I missed some it's may be
possible
coal land
are they more likely to be near other
things no no it's great well that lasted
then I gotta find my way back can you
not is that an actual thing like you
could not turn on diamonds what do you
remember how to go back all these card I
just start to look the same
[Music]
they all just go in circles I wish these
branches have been designed by
see ya - this is the Ramanujan
[Music]
okay
138 well that's where I am 6x6 tunnels
what's a 6x6 top
[Music]
oh there's a room hey you think it
through them because you're a stupid
thingy and I'm gonna get here
see any diamond everything else
three verse you dedicate more RAM to my
car it's not lagging for me it's only
lighting for you guys oh this is insane
I walked through this whole cave no
diamonds there's more cave
[Music]
great we did okay okay okay okay we're
doing those coordinates after you go get
my stuff back
we got five minutes something I remember
the way back please write and flash not
all my things
okay let's get out of here
no monster can make it through that okay
where are the diamonds 108 eight 121 108
108 a interrogator download that 108 8
121 okay guys
where are diamonds
where are they I'm starting to think
there are no diamonds just trying to
think of the RAM and my computer
glitched I'm starting to think guys that
this is the past and the Diamonds
haven't been made yet that's the only
explanation that makes any sense to me
we must be in the past
otherwise there'd be diamonds but there
aren't any diamonds so therefore if you
found this beautiful cave like this
would be the perfect place for there to
be some diamonds except to heart because
I don't think diamonds are enabled on
this server I'm not even sure really
what that means it doesn't it sound
we've been digging for diamonds now for
an hour we've cheated
and we haven't found diamonds we've dug
forever
not a single diamond was found the only
conclusion is that they don't exist
okay 108 121 108 8 121 108 8 101 not 108
Oh 101 all right yeah we're gonna wait
at 101 let's go sorry it's hard to dig
with this thing on my screen
guys look at that right where you all
said they were oh sweet diamond Oh
beautiful diamond I have dug for days
in hopes to find you I stopped believing
in you and I shouldn't have and for that
I'm sorry
you guys here you lay right
it only took a little bit of cheating
twitch I'm so proud of all of you to
everyone who came through here today to
make what's about to happen possible let
me just throw away some of my stupid
cobblestone control gee how do I throw
this away
how do I throw this away alt Q
[Music]
goodbye enjoy the whole today we mine
diamonds for glorious beautiful diamonds
the music is just perfect for this
occasion I'm not even sure how to get
out of here
I'm not sure how I got down here but it
doesn't matter because I have diamonds
and that guy's I think is the end of our
minecraft stream I feel so unbelievably
accomplished even though we cheated
badly well why don't we just do that at
the beginning why don't we just look up
where everything is
[Music]
let me wait no no no no putting the
music back we need the music
we need the music we need the music but
I want to also do this
wait no no no no no go over here go over
here yeah that's right that's right
ah guess we have four diamonds
[Music]
I'm not even sure what you do with
diamonds but we have four of them we get
it together nice food one kick and one
shovel should we go to the nether are we
close to the meta okay guys
you stuck with me this long let's make
my box small and let's go to the nether
if I ever find the way out of here I'm
not sure how easy that is get in here
okay we need ten obsidian how do we
obtain obsidian well this is the one
that we never put torches on there's no
diamond
since fire is this our og as our G
crafting table
should I make a diamond ho oh this one
right all right so fast oh that was dumb
that was so good
all right yo diamond ho never waste your
diamonds on oh that's that's good advice
yes all right
make a bucket do we have it on fire on I
hope we do there we go
how to make bucket
called her
bah dad perfect guys I'm afraid I'm
gonna fall into the lava okay oh look
look at all this weeds tonight we eat
I'll look at all that weed - I know we
walked on the farm and it was terrible
but all right we got water now I know
what this lava it's like up on the hill
right
a little outdoor crafting
we have food now everything is looking
up for us it was on the hill alright
there's like a lava pool is easier to
find at night
I fall in the lava you know what I'm
gonna save the game no no that's weak no
I'm not gonna do that
if we die we die but if we live we live
you need to copy to save you that all
sounds too hard there was lava here
right remember that lava pool
this was the fake cave
what's that bad trading in minecraft oh
there's our old remember that thing well
so maybe it was on that side of the
thing if there's definitely easier ways
to find lava to
you know with this lava you know just go
in my mind i knows love in my mind
should go to the mine gotta mine and
actually I don't know what his lava in
mine
and what is love in the other mine oh
yeah lovak Awards all I love u k-- award
grows yak award bros
she's you know fine at night
okay well we can just go down here I'm
sure there's a lot more down here if
there's not as they're monsters down
here there might be monsters as I seal
this off no nevermind I'll go down
anymore as creepy I saw the lava
make armor with the iron good no my
water but spread like crazy
make a flint and steel again I need it
for the portal oh well let's take this
one step at a time
I see ash is that from lava no I did
that again
now what's down here it's lava not lava
okay wait lava is that what are we
anywhere near there nineteen
guys I'm gonna get lost
oh no that's does the river by my house
okay nineteen we go got water and ghost
was the love I found before I love
cheating bro Oh cheating grows the best
I was right here before
hola I'm scared I'm gonna fall how do I
use water how oh yeah buddy I took it
back
the it's raining
oh I lost my obsidian well that was
rather dumb
I'm out of space
eight enemies
go move
which oh I need to get ten of these
oh it's nighttime
yeah go
you got tomorrow you Freddie Freddie
brain oh yeah
okay guys I remember where the lava is
we'll be back tomorrow when the rains up
I'll have a bright new day in Minecraft
where we're gonna go to the nether then
we're gonna shut this off cuz then
we're done
whoa good night's sleep gasps what's
that noise
now you go back to the obses back to
them what but be you adapt to my diamond
pickaxe that's right and now I'm gonna
eat some bread cuz we have please do
some outdoor crafts
Oh cooking stream
that's just what I was thinking
directrix 13 more water always useful
she even get my shovel out
okay so here's that the lavas like
somewhere around here
[Music]
negative 19
hear us
[Music]
oh yeah want some bread guys kind of a
mood for some bread
so bud are we doing all we need one more
[Music]
you've got an extra one for good luck
they break it just takes a really long
time
I read that online hey cool
we have 11 leave a granite monument for
how to find lava the monument to lava
that's a much quicker way to go it seems
okay so we're gonna go home oh that
looks nice let's eat it we're gonna go
home
we have our obsidian now we need to make
a flint and steel to ignite the portal
and how do we make the port
well my five let's say oh wait this is
like oh so four by five wait but don't I
need more obsidian for that what do I
not need to do the corners and when you
flint and steel tell which thank you man
we have flint
it seems useful
you only inside inner corners okay okay
we're gonna build it right here y'all
thought I was building that Cabos no
wait I didn't stone - okay perfect
no inside of no corners - we'll go there
we won we'll go that way what minecraft
and nether portal just look at images oh
this one's good yeah here we go
one two three four okay I understand how
it's icsf oh we're doing it right
let me just build a lovely staircase to
my nether portal
Oh construction crew working wait oh I
guess I can do this okay
now for the moment of truth haha we did
boys we did it let's go it didn't work
let's try again
oh yeah alright guys you know what
I have a plan we got to go home we gotta
get something though I love wearing that
there portal as much as the next guy we
do have to go get something hmm one
white wall let's go find some sheep I
think I'm gonna go take a nap in the
medic you know I'm gonna go sleep in the
nether no I think we just make bed don't
look ever since the rain storm we have
this red flood here she pees you she you
know what I have a better idea guys we
don't even need she pees we'll just take
it with us let's go it's not like we'll
be coming back I'm moving into the
nether for good I'm moving into the
nether forever I'll just bring it with
us
perfect
oh wow place seems pretty nice I'm just
gonna bury should explore a little first
and then we're gonna sleep all right
guys good night
it's been it's been a great stream but
uh I'll see you all I'll see you all I'm
going I'm going to sleep I'll see you
all see you all later